https://www.deepblue.com/terms-of-service/

General
D E E P B L U E Digital LLC comprehends that your security is critical to you. We are focused on securing the protection of your actually recognizable data as you utilize this site. This Privacy Policy discloses to you how we secure and use data that we accumulate from you. By utilizing this site, you agree to the terms depicted in the latest rendition of this Privacy Policy. You should likewise peruse our Terms of Use to comprehend the general guidelines about your utilization of this site, and any extra terms that may apply when you get to specific administrations or materials on specific territories of this site. “We,” “our” signifies D E E P B L U E Digital, LLC and its associates. “You,” “your,” guest,” or “client” signifies the individual getting to this site.
INDIVIDUAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
Our Privacy Policy distinguishes how we treat your own and non-individual data.
WHAT IS NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION AND HOW IS IT COLLECTED AND USED?
Non individual data is data that can’t recognize you. On the off chance that you visit this site to understand data, for example, data around one of our administrations, we may gather certain non-individual data about you from your PC’s internet browser. Since non-individual data can’t distinguish you or be attached to you in any capacity, there are no limitations on the manners in which that we can utilize or share non-individual data. What is close to home data and how is it gathered? Individual data is data that distinguishes you as an individual, for example, your name, street number, email address, phone number, and fax number. We may gather individual data from you in an assortment of ways: • When you send us an application or other structure • When you lead an exchange with us, our partners, or others • When we gather data about in you on the side of an exchange, for example, charge card data • In certain spots on this site you have the chance to send us individual data about yourself, to choose to get specific data, to buy access to one of our items or administrations, or to take an interest in a movement.
ARE COOKIES OR OTHER TECHNOLOGIES USED TO COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Indeed, we may utilize treats and related advances, for example, web reference points, to gather data on our site. A treat is a book document that is put on your hard circle by a page server. Treats can’t be utilized to run programs or convey infections to your PC. Treats are remarkably relegated to you, and must be perused by a web server in the area that gave the treat to you. One of the basic roles of treats is to give an accommodation highlight to spare you time. The motivation behind a treat is to tell the Web server that you have come back to a particular page. For instance, in the event that you register with us, a treat helps D E E P L U E Digital LLC to review your particular data on ensuing visits. This improves the way toward recording your own data, for example, charging addresses, delivering addresses, etc. At the point when you come back to a similar D E E P L U E Digital LLC site, the data you recently gave can be recovered, so you can without much of a stretch utilize the highlights that you modified. A web reference point is a little realistic picture that permits the gathering that set the web signal to screen and gather certain data about the watcher of the page, online report or email message, for example, the sort of program mentioning the web guide, the IP address of the PC that the web guide is sent to and the time the web reference point was seen. Web reference points can be extremely little and undetectable to the client, at the same time, when all is said in done, any electronic picture saw as a feature of a website page or email, including HTML based substance, can go about as a web signal. We may utilize web reference points to check guests to the site pages on the site or to screen how our clients explore the site, and we may incorporate web guides in email messages so as to tally what number of messages sent were really opened, followed up on or sent.
Outsider sellers likewise may utilize treats on our site. For example, we may contract with outsiders who will utilize treats on our site to follow and break down mysterious utilization and volume measurable data from our guests and individuals. Such data is shared remotely just on an unknown, collected premise. These outsiders utilize diligent treats to assist us with improving the guest experience, to deal with our site content, and to follow guest conduct. We may likewise contract with an outsider to send email to our enrolled clients.
To help gauge and improve the viability of our email correspondences, the outsider sets treats. All information gathered by this outsider in the interest of D E E P L U E Digital LLC is utilized exclusively by or in the interest of D E E P L U E Digital LLC and is shared remotely just on a mysterious, accumulated premise. Occasionally we may permit outsiders to post ads on our site, and those outsider commercials may incorporate a treat or web guide served by the outsider. This Privacy Policy doesn’t cover the utilization of data gathered from you by outsider advertisement servers. We don’t control treats in such outsider promotions, and you should check the security approaches of those sponsors as well as advertisement administrations to find out about their utilization of treats and other innovation before connecting to a promotion. We won’t share your own data with these organizations, yet these organizations may utilize data about your visits to this and other sites so as to give ads on this site and different locales about products and enterprises that might bear some significance with you, and they may share your own data that you furnish to them with others.
You can acknowledge or decrease treats. Most Web programs naturally acknowledge treats, yet you can for the most part change your program setting to decay treats on the off chance that you like. In the event that you decide to decay treats, you will be unable to completely encounter the intuitive highlights of the D E E P L U E Digital LLC sites you visit.
HOW DOES D E E P L U E DIGITAL LLC USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?
D E E P L U E Digital LLC may keep and utilize individual data we gather from or about you to give you access to this site or different items or administrations, to react to your solicitations, to charge you for items/administrations you bought, and to offer progressing assistance and backing, to reach you with data that may hold any importance with you, including data about items and administrations of our own and of others, or request your assessment about our items or the results of others, for record keeping and systematic purposes and to investigate, create and improve programs, items, administrations and substance.
Individual data gathered online might be joined with data you give to us through different sources We may likewise expel your own identifiers (your name, email address, government managed savings number, and so on). For this situation, you would never again be distinguished as a solitary exceptional person. When we have de-distinguished data, it is non-individual data and we may treat it like other non-individual data. At last, we may utilize your own data to ensure our privileges or property, or to secure somebody’s wellbeing, wellbeing or government assistance, and to follow a law or guideline, court request or other lawful procedure.
DOES D E E P L U E DIGITAL LLC SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHERS?
We won’t share your own data gathered from this site with an inconsequential outsider without your consent, aside from as in any case gave in this Privacy Policy. In the conventional course of business, we may impart some close to home data to organizations that we recruit to perform administrations or capacities for our benefit. In all cases where we share your own data with an outsider to offer a support to us, we won’t approve them to keep, uncover or utilize your data with others aside from the motivation behind offering the types of assistance we requested that they give.
We won’t sell, trade or distribute your own data, aside from related to a corporate deal, merger, disintegration, or securing. For such exchanges, notwithstanding our immediate assortment of data, our outsider help merchants, (for example, Visa organizations, clearinghouses and banks) who may offer such types of assistance as credit, protection, and escrow administrations may gather individual data legitimately from you to help you with your exchange. We don’t control how these outsiders utilize such data, yet we do request that they reveal how they utilize your own data before they gather it.
On the off chance that you present a survey for an outsider (individual or business) utilizing our Facebook Fan Review Application, during the accommodation procedure we request that your authorization accumulate your essential data, (for example, name and email address) which we at that point share with the outsider for whom you are presenting the audit. We might be lawfully constrained to discharge your own data because of a court request, summon, court order, law or guideline.
We may help out law requirement experts in exploring and arraigning site guests who abuse our standards or take part in conduct, which is destructive to different guests (or illicit). We may unveil your own data to outsiders on the off chance that we feel that the divulgence is important to secure our privileges or property, ensure somebody’s wellbeing, security or government assistance, or to conform to a law or guideline, court request or other legitimate procedure. As talked about in the area on treats and different innovations, every once in a while we may permit an outsider to serve notices on this site.
On the off chance that you share data with the promoter, including by tapping on their advertisements, this Privacy Policy doesn’t control the publicists utilization of your own data.
Constraint of Liability
By no means, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE, SHALL WE, OUR SUBSIDIARY AND PARENT COMPANIES OR AFFILIATES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE SITE, INCLUDING OUR MESSAGING, BLOGS, COMMENTS OF OTHERS, BOOKS, EMAILS, PRODUCTS, OR SERVICES, OR THIRD-PARTY MATERIALS, PRODUCTS, OR SERVICES MADE AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE OR BY US IN ANY WAY, EVEN IF WE ARE ADVISED BEFOREHAND OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. (Since SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN CATEGORIES OF DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, OUR LIABILITY AND THE LIABILITY OF OUR SUBSIDIARY AND PARENT COMPANIES OR AFFILIATES IS LIMITED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY SUCH STATE LAW.) YOU SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT WE ARE NOT LIABLE FOR ANY DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF ANY USER. In the event that YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH THE SITE, ANY MATERIALS, PRODUCTS, OR SERVICES ON THE SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THE SITE’S TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE SITE AND THE PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND/OR MATERIALS COMPANY IS NOT AN INVESTMENT ADVISORY SERVICE, IS NOT AN INVESTMENT ADVISER, AND DOES NOT PROVIDE PERSONALIZED FINANCIAL ADVICE OR ACT AS A FINANCIAL ADVISOR.
WE EXIST FOR EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY, AND THE MATERIALS AND INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN AND IN OUR PRODUCTS AND SERVICES ARE FOR GENERAL INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. NONE OF THE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY US IS INTENDED AS INVESTMENT, TAX, ACCOUNTING OR LEGAL ADVICE, AS AN OFFER OR SOLICITATION OF AN OFFER TO BUY OR SELL, OR AS AN ENDORSEMENT, RECOMMENDATION OR SPONSORSHIP OF ANY COMPANY, SECURITY, OR FUND. OUR INFORMATION SHOULD NOT BE RELIED UPON FOR PURPOSES OF TRANSACTING IN SECURITIES OR OTHER INVESTMENTS.
WE DO NOT OFFER OR PROVIDE TAX, LEGAL OR INVESTMENT ADVICE AND YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR CONSULTING TAX, LEGAL, OR FINANCIAL PROFESSIONALS BEFORE ACTING ON ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED BY US. THIS SITE IS CONTINUALLY UNDER DEVELOPMENT AND COMPANY MAKES NO WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, IMPLIED OR EXPRESS, AS TO ITS ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR APPROPRIATENESS FOR ANY PURPOSE.
YOU recognize and concurs that no portrayal has been made by COMPANY OR ITS AFFILIATES and depended upon with regards to the future salary, costs, deals volume or potential gainfulness that might be gotten from the support in THIS PROGRAM.
End
We may drop or end your entitlement to utilize the Site or any piece of the Site whenever without notice. In case of wiping out or end, you are not, at this point approved to get to the piece of the Site influenced by such undoing or end. The limitations forced on you concerning material downloaded from the Site, and the disclaimers and impediments of liabilities set out in these Terms of Service, will endure.
Discount Policy
Your acquisition of an item or administration or pass to an occasion could conceivably accommodate any discount. Every particular item, administration, occasion or course will indicate its own discount strategy.
Other
The Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (the “DMCA”) gives plan of action to copyright proprietors who accept that material showing up on the Internet encroaches their privileges under the U.S. copyright law. On the off chance that you have confidence in accordance with some basic honesty that materials facilitated by COMPANY encroach your copyright, you, or your specialist may send to COMPANY a notification mentioning that the material be expelled or access to it be blocked. Any notice by a copyright proprietor or an individual approved to follow up for its benefit that neglects to agree to prerequisites of the DMCA will not be viewed as adequate notification and will not be considered to give upon COMPANY real information on realities or conditions from which encroaching material or acts are apparent. On the off chance that you put stock in accordance with some basic honesty that a notification of copyright encroachment has been wrongly recorded against you, the DMCA grants you to send to COMPANY a counter-notice. All notification and counter notification must meet the then current legal prerequisites forced by the DMCA; see http://www.loc.gov/copyright for subtleties. Organization’s Copyright Agent for notice of cases of copyright encroachment or counter notification can be reached as follows: support@samovens.com
This Agreement will be authoritative upon and acclimate to the advantage of COMPANY and our individual allocates, replacements, beneficiaries, and legitimate delegates. Neither this Agreement nor any rights hereunder might be allocated without the earlier composed assent of COMPANY. Despite the prior, all rights and commitments under this Agreement might be uninhibitedly appointed by COMPANY to any subsidiary element or any of its completely claimed auxiliaries
These Terms of Use will be administered by and interpreted as per the laws of the State of California and any debate will be liable to restricting assertion in ­­California. On the off chance that any arrangement of this understanding will be unlawful, void or in any way, shape or form unenforceable, at that point that arrangement will be esteemed severable from this understanding and will not influence the legitimacy and enforceability of any residual arrangements.
Disclaimer
In spite of the fact that it is profoundly far-fetched, This approach might be changed whenever at our watchfulness. In the event that we should refresh this approach, we will present the reports on this page on our Website.
In the event that you have any inquiries or concerns with respect to our protection strategy please direct them to: support@deepblue.com
We would love to hear about your project. Let’s talk.
contact
San Francisco388 Market StSuite 1300
San Francisco, CA 94111(415) 228-6861
Atlanta1201 W Peachtree St NW Suite 2300Atlanta, GA 30309(404) 860-1555
